[left hand] grasp the stack of blocks | [right hand] support the stack | [ego] stay still
[left hand] lift the orange triangular block | [right hand] lift the red triangular block | [both hands] separate the blocks
[left hand] place the orange triangular block on the table | [right hand] lift the green triangular block from the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] lift the green triangular block | [left hand] hold the remaining stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the green triangular block on the table | [left hand] lift the green square block from the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the green triangular block on the table | [left hand] lift the green square block | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the green triangular block on the table | [left hand] lift the blue triangular block from the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the blue triangular block on the table | [left hand] lift the blue triangular block from the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the blue triangular block on the table | [left hand] lift the green square block from the stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the green square block on the table | [left hand] hold the remaining stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] lift the green square block from the stack | [left hand] hold the remaining stack | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the green square block on the table | [ego] stay still
[right hand] pick up a green square block from the stack | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the green square block on the table | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] pick up an orange square block from the stack | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the orange square block on the table | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] pick up a blue square block from the stack | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the blue square block on the table | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] pick up a yellow square block from the stack | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the yellow square block on the table | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] pick up a pink square block from the stack | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the pink square block on the table | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] pick up a purple square block from the stack | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the purple square block on the table | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] pick up a blue square block from the stack | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still
[right hand] place the blue square block on the table | [left hand] hold the remaining stack steady | [ego] stay still